(Santa:)Santa thinks dating you
may be punishment enough.
(Sheldon:)There's an argument
for that.
(Sheldon:)But I want to make sure.
(Photographer:)Smile.
Ho, ho, ho!
(Leonard:)Okay. On the
count of three,
(Leonard:)I'll shoot the fire extinguisher
and get him airborne.
(Leonard:)Howard, you wave the blanket
and guide him towards the exit.
(Leonard:)Raj, you hold open the
curtain so he can fly out.
(Howard:)Are you sure a dummy
like me can handle something
(Howard:)as complicated
as a blanket?
(Leonard:)Do you want the
fire extinguisher?
(Howard:)Yeah, I do.
Great.
(Leonard:)Here you go.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Howard:)One, two, three.
(Raj:)Uh, you have to
take the pin out.
(Leonard:)You miss the blanket now,
don't you?
(Howard:)On three.